(Penny:)that makes you
a little insecure.
(Leonard:)Well, I can't believe
you'd say that.
(Leonard:)You know how insecure I am
about my insecurities.
(Penny:)You know what?
I'm sorry.
(Penny:)It's stupid
to fight over money.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
We're about to share
(Leonard:)the rest of our lives together.
It's our money--
who cares who has it?
Ugh! You're right--
who cares? Mm.
(Penny:)Get that money
out of my back pocket
(Penny:)or I will break your fingers.
(Raj:)Huh. All this time
I never knew
(Raj:)there were steam tunnels
down here.
(Amy:)Most universities
have them.
(Amy:)When I was an undergrad,
I spent three days in one
(Amy:)pledging a sorority.
(Raj:)Did you get in?
(Amy:)No. They forgot I was there.
(Amy:)But it really opened up
my pores.
(Sheldon:)Well, according
to my research,
(Sheldon:)the steam tunnels
below this access point
(Sheldon:)should be the closest
analog to the mines.
(Raj:)This is gonna be
so much more accurate
(Raj:)than the steam room at the gym.
(Sheldon:)Plus, there's almost no chance
(Sheldon:)we'll see any
of our coworkers half naked.